I learned about the Negro National Anthem
in the back seat of a purple Dodge Neon
my sophomore year of high school,
sitting next to my best friend,
a white girl named Julia.
And Julia was like,
I just feel like being friends with you all.
I should know your anthem.
And I was like, yeah, bitch.
We know your anthem.
Someday somebody's gonna make you
wanna turn around and say goodbye.
Till then, baby,
are you gonna let them hold you down
and make you cry?
Don't you know?
It's a shame.
Things will go your way.
If you're...
Oh, God.
That's all black girls
that grew up with white girls.
I am you.
You were the only black girl
at the slumber party.
You were going in the pool
with a shower cap.
Yes.
Keisha, teach us how to dance.
Teach us how to dance.
Yeah.
You're like black
when I like black, black.
You know what I mean?
Oh, God.